{
    "html":[
        {
            "question": "Which attribute replaces the name attribute for the following elements: a, applet, frame, iframe, img, and map?",
            "options": ["The src attribute","The class attribute","The id attribute","The name attribute"],
            "answer": "C"
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you display a border like this: The top border = 10 pixels The bottom border = 5 pixelsThe left border = 20 pixelsThe right border = 1 pixel?",
            "options": ["border-width: 10px 1px 5px 20px","border-width: 10px 20px 5px 1px","border-width: 5px 20px 10px 1px","border-width: 5px 10px 20px 1px"],
            "answer": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "The HTML global attribute, 'contenteditable' is used to:",
            "options": ["Update content from the srever","Return the position of the first found occurrence of content inside a string","Specify whether the content of an element should be editable or not","Specifies a context menu for an element .The menu appears when a user right-clicks on the element"],
            "answer": "C"
        },
        {
            "question": "Increasing the cellpadding value will what?",
            "options": ["Increase the softness of your site","Increase the space between cells","Increase the distance between cell and content","Increase the space between cells and elements"],
            "answer": "C"
        },
        {
            "question": "In HTML, onblur and onfocus are:",
            "options": ["Event attributes","Style attributes","HTML elements","No special character"],
            "answer": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "Graphics defined by SVG is in which format?",
            "options": ["HTML","CSS","XML","PHP"],
            "answer": "C"
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you display hyperlinks without an underline?",
            "options": ["a {underline: none}","a {text-decoration: none}","a {text-decoration: no underline}","a {decoration: no underline}"],
            "answer": "B"
        },
        {
            "question": "What does an HTML tag do?",
            "options": ["It specifies formatting and layout instructions for your web page","It hides programming instructions from view","It connects your web site to an operating environment","It determines the organizational structure of your Web site"],
            "answer": "D"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which HTML element is used to display a scalar measurement within a range?",
            "options": ["&lt; measure &gt","&lt; meter &gt","&lt; range &gt","&lt; gauge &gt"],
            "answer": "B"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where in an HTML document is the correct place to refer to an external style sheet?",
            "options": ["In the < body > section","In the < head > section","At the top of the document","At the end of the document"],
            "answer": "B"
        }
    ]
}
